(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T09:20:10.001324",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は『hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish』
Today, for "hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish"
Supported by ヴァイスシュヴァルツ DAY1にご来場いただきまして、
Supported by Weiß Schwarz DAY 1, thank you for attending.
誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ご来場いただきまして、ご来場のお客様にお願いがございます。
We have a request for all visitors attending the venue.
新型コロナウイルス感染拡大防止対策として、マスクの着用、手指の消毒、ソーシャルディスタンスのご協力をお願いしております。
As a measure to prevent the spread of the novel coronavirus, we ask for your cooperation with wearing masks, hand disinfection, and social distancing.
お見かけの際やロビー内でも、お客様同士の距離間隔を保っていただくようご協力をお願いいたします。
Even when passing each other or inside the lobby, we kindly ask you to maintain distance between customers.
飛沫防止のため、声出しなどはご遠慮いただきますようお願い申し上げます。
To prevent droplet infection, please refrain from shouting or cheering.
入場時に検温にて体調確認をさせていただいておりますが、万が一、体調に異変を感じた場合は無理をせずスタッフへお声がけください。
We check temperatures and health conditions upon entry, but if you feel any sudden illness, please do not overexert yourself and speak to a staff member.
客席内での携帯電話、スマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones is prohibited inside the seating area.
スマートフォンは新型コロナウイルス接触確認アプリCOCOAを使用するため、電源はお切りにならず開演までにマナーモードへ設定しておしまいください。
Since smartphones use the COVID-19 contact-confirming app COCOA, please do not turn off the power, but set them to manner mode before the show begins.
また、携帯電話などによる撮影、録音、録画は固くお断りいたします。
Also, photography, audio recording, and video recording using mobile phones or similar devices are strictly prohibited.
万が一発見した場合は、データ削除の上、退場していただく場合がございます。
If discovered, you may be asked to leave after having your data deleted.
客席内での飲食、ライブ、ジャンプ等の激しい行為、ルールに反したコンサートライトの使用は禁止となります。
Eating and drinking, jumping, and other high-energy activities, as well as using concert lights in violation of the rules, are prohibited inside the seating area.
以上のことが守られない場合は、公演を一時中断もしくは中止させていただく可能性がございます。
If these rules are not followed, the performance may be temporarily suspended or canceled.
また、本公演では、自席の前にお立ちいただくことを許可しております。
Also, in this performance, standing up in front of your own seat is permitted.
このほか、本公演は避難誘導等の消灯を行います。
In addition, this performance will turn off some lights for evacuation guidance.
万が一、避難が必要になった場合は、すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、係員の指示に従っていただきますようお願いいたします。
In the unlikely event that evacuation is necessary, emergency lights will be turned on immediately, so please follow the staff's instructions.
公演終了後は危険防止、またソーシャルディスタンス確保のため、ブロックごとの規制退場にご協力のほどよろしくお願いいたします。スタッフの指示があるまでご自分の席でお待ちください。
After the performance, to prevent hazards and ensure social distance, we ask for your cooperation with staggered block exits. Please wait in your seat until instructed by the staff.
最後に、本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、お客様の様子が映り込む可能性がございます。これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、予めご了解ください。
Finally, please note that cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue during this performance, and attendees may be captured on camera. These videos and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes, so please understand this in advance.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a little while until the performance begins.
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション
Booster Pack Hololive Production
好評発売中！
On sale now!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We are the Chugai Mining Content Dept., huge fans of anime!
もっともっと！
Wanting to enjoy
アニメを楽しみたい
anime more and more,
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発してインターネットで販売しています！
we plan, develop, and sell anime merchandise online with that passion!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます
We also run anime-collaboration cafes!
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check Twitter for the latest info!
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Notice to Visitors]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attention: Notice to Visitors]
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 1
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attention: Notice to Visitors]
Attention: To all visitors
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please refrain from cheering aloud during the performance
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション
Premium Booster: hololive production
2022年3月19日(土)、20日(日)開催にて発売!
On sale at the expo on March 19-20, 2022!
ブシロードアクリルカードスタンド / カードバインダー
Bushirod Acrylic Card Stand & Binder
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
Plate Acrylic Stand & B2 Tapestry
耐水シール 全31種 各660円
Waterproof Stickers (31 types) - ¥660 each
缶&ハンドタオル 各1,650円
Can Badge & Hand Towel - ¥1,650 each
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all visitors
公演中は自席の前で立ってご観覧いただけます
You may view while standing in front of your seat
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY1
3rd fes. 公式アイテム ペンライト・Tシャツ
3rd fes. Official Items: Penlight & T-shirts
3rd fes. ペンライトカラーまとめ
3rd fes. Penlight Colors Guide
ウィンドブレーカー / トートバッグ / サコッシュ
Windbreaker / Tote Bag / Sacoche
ロゴクッション / ラバーバンド / タペストリー
Logo Cushion / Rubber Band / Tapestry
EN×NEW ERA コラボキャップ / サラサクリップ5色セット
EN x NEW ERA Cap / SARASA Clip Set (5 colors)
ランダム缶バッジ
Random Can Badges
アクリルキーホルダー 各1,700円
Acrylic Keychains - ¥1,700 each
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Unstoppable even in hololive production booster packs, Weiß Schwarz!
ブシロードパック
Bushiroad pack,
ホロライブプロダクション 好評発売中！
hololive production booster pack is now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad.
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We are Chugai Mining's content department, who love anime!
もっともっと！
More and more!
アニメを楽しきたい！
We want to enjoy anime!
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発してインターネットで販売しています！
With that passion, we plan and develop anime merchandise and sell it online!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます
We also run anime-collaboration cafes!
最新情報はTwitterで！
Get the latest info on Twitter!
ホロライブ6期生のラプラス・ダークネスです。
I'm Laplace Darkness of hololive 6th generation.
本日は「hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish」
Today, at "hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish",
にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
thank you very much for coming.
同じく、
Along with...
ホロライブ3rd fes.
hololive 3rd fes.
ロッキンセー！
Rockin' say...!
ロックスの頭脳、
Rox's brain,
白銀ノエルだよー！
Shirogane Noel here!
今日は私たちが場内アナウンスを担当します。
Today, we'll be in charge of the venue announcements.
今日一日、よろしくねー！
Have a wonderful day today, everyone!
ホロライブ6期生の鷹嶺ルイです。
This is Takane Lui of hololive 6th Generation.
開演の前に、お客さまにご案内がございます。
Before the doors open, we have some announcements for our guests.
まず初めに、会場の皆様へのご案内です。
First, some instructions for everyone in the venue.
ロビー、客席内では、マスクの着用が必須となります。
Wearing a mask is mandatory in the lobby and seating areas.
講演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点からご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from shouting or cheering during the performance to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
是非、拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いいたします。
Instead, please show your support with applause and penlights.
また、会場内では立って応援いただいても問題ございませんが、
Also, while standing to cheer inside the venue is permitted,
周りのお客さまのご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮をお願いいたします。
please be considerate so as not to cause any inconvenience to those around you.
続いて、配信をご覧の皆様へご案内です。
Next, an announcement for everyone watching the stream.
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信やビデオアップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirror streaming, or uploading videos of this live performance is strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットで撮影をしていただくことやSNSで感想をつぶやいていただくは大歓迎なので、
Instead, taking screenshots and tweeting your impressions on social media is very welcome,
皆さん、ハッシュタグ「つながるホロライブDAY1」で感想をつぶやいてSNSもいっぱい盛り上げてください！
so please post your thoughts on social media using the hashtag #つながるホロライブDAY1 and liven things up!
Hello everyone, this is Irys from Hololive EN Project HOPE.
Hello everyone, this is IRyS from hololive English -Project HOPE-.
Thank you for coming to hololive 3rd Fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 1 today.
Similarly, I am Sana from Hololive EN Council.
And I am Tsukumo Sana from hololive English -Council-.
Today, we will be in charge of all the announcements within the venue.
We hope you have an amazing time.
Likewise, I am Fauna from hololive English -Council-.
Before we start the show, we have some quick announcements.
We would first like to address the audience here today.
Masks are mandatory and must be worn in the lobby and audience seats.
Please refrain from shouting during the performances in order to prevent the spread of coronavirus.
We would love it if you supported us with your hands and penlights.
In addition, it is fine to stand up and cheer within the venue, however, please be considerate of those around you when doing so.
Next is a short reminder to all of you who will be watching the livestream. It is strictly prohibited to record, tape, mirror, or illegally upload this live performance.
However, in return, you are definitely welcome to take screenshots and tweet about your experience on all social media platforms. Please use the hashtag #つながるホロライブDAY1 and tweet your thoughts on social media.
This live performance is expected to require a large amount of data transmission and bandwidth. We heavily recommend that you use Wi-Fi when viewing this event on your smartphones. If your internet connection is unstable, we cannot guarantee the quality of the delivered video.
Halo semuanya, namaku Risu dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi Kedua.
Halo semuanya! Namaku Risu dari hololive Indonesia Gen 2.
Terima kasih telah datang ke Hololive 3rd Fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 1!
Dan aku Anya dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
Dan aku Anya dari hololive Indonesia Gen 2.
Hari ini kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk membacakan pengumuman.
Semoga hari ini akan jadi hari yang menyenangkan!
Halo semuanya, namaku Reine dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
Halo semuanya! Namaku Reine dari hololive Indonesia Gen 2.
Pertama-tama ada beberapa pengumuman untuk para tamu.
Kepada para tamu, kami mohon untuk selalu memakai masker saat berada di lobi maupun...
tempat-tempat duduk.
seating.
Kami mohon juga untuk tidak mengeluarkan suara pada saat konser untuk mencegah penyebaran virus corona.
We also kindly ask that you refrain from making noise during the concert to prevent the spread of the coronavirus.
Mohon dukung kami dengan tepukan tangan dan juga penlight ya!
Please support us with applause and penlights too!
Selanjutnya adalah pengumuman untuk para pendatang yang menonton livestream.
Next is an announcement for attendees watching the livestream.
Anda dilarang untuk merekam, menayangkan, atau mengupload ulang stream konser secara ilegal.
You are prohibited from illegally recording, broadcasting, or re-uploading the concert stream.
Tetapi sebagai gantinya, Anda dianjurkan untuk upload screenshot
Instead, you are encouraged to upload screenshots
dan posting mengenai konser kami di media sosial! Mari gunakan tagar #SenagarHololiveDay1 di media sosial saat posting kesanmu mengenai acara ini.
and post about our concert on social media! Let's use the hashtag #SenagarHololiveDay1 on social media when posting your thoughts about this event.
Karena konser live ini akan menggunakan data berukuran besar,
Because this live concert will use a large amount of data,
kami menyarankan penggunaan Wi-Fi jika Anda menonton dari smartphone.
we recommend using Wi-Fi if you are watching from a smartphone.
Jika kualitas koneksi internet Anda tidak memadai, kami tidak bisa menjanjikan kualitas video.
If your internet connection quality is inadequate, we cannot promise video quality.
Kami mohon pengertiannya.
We ask for your understanding.
Kami berkomitmen untuk mempersiapkan livestream ini dengan sebaik mungkin.
We are committed to preparing this livestream as best as possible.
Namun, karena ini merupakan acara yang tayang secara langsung, tetap ada kemungkinan terjadinya masalah teknis.
However, because this is a live-broadcasted event, there is still a possibility of technical issues occurring.
Kami mohon pengertiannya ya.
We ask for your understanding.
Hari ini adalah hololive 3rd fes Link Your...
Today is hololive 3rd fes. Link Your...
hololive 3rd fes. Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ Day1にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for attending hololive 3rd fes. Supported by Weiß Schwarz Day 1.
まもなく開演するよー！
The show is about to start!
みんな、準備はいい？
Everyone, are you ready?
せーの！
Ready, set!
Day1、スタート！
Day 1, start!
AZKi
さくらみこ
[Sakura Miko]
星街すいせい
[Hoshimachi Suisei]
赤井はあと
[Akai Haato]
白上フブキ
[Shirakami Fubuki]
夏色まつり
[Natsuiro Matsuri]
大空スバル
[Oozora Subaru]
戌神ころね
[Inugami Korone]
白銀ノエル
[Shirogane Noel]
宝鐘マリン
[Houshou Marine]
天音かなた
[Amane Kanata]
常闇トワ
[Tokoyami Towa]
姫森ルーナ
[Himemori Luna]
桃鈴ねね
[Momosuzu Nene]
尾丸ポルカ
[Omaru Polka]
一伊那爾栖
[Ninomae Ina'nis]
がうる・ぐら
[Gawr Gura]
ワトソン・アメリア
[Watson Amelia]
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
[Moona Hoshinova]
同じ未来を見たい あの夢手に入れたい
I want to see the same future, I want to take that dream in my hands
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ go!
Run with your own unique heart, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
In a place where it was pitch dark no matter where I looked,
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
My eyes were stolen by a tiny hope sprouting up.
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my heart that trembles with anxiety,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I mustered up just a little bit of courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
Deleting the word "give up," I move forward.
苦しいときも、もう私はひとりじゃないから
Even when it's painful, I'm no longer alone anymore.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
That's why I want to chase my dreams even more, the excitement won't stop
想像越えてく世界 見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that goes beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ go!
Run with your own unique heart, go!
だからもっと夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
That's why I want to chase my dreams even more, the excitement won't stop
鼓動を超えてく世界 見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that goes beyond the heartbeat.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違ったココロで 走れ go!
Run with your own unique heart, go!
あいあい あいあい あいらぶゆー
Ai-ai, ai-ai, I love you!
もう あいあい あいあい あい にじゅー
Mou, ai-ai, ai-ai, I need you!
もっと
Motto
( もっと )
(Motto)
もっと
Motto
( もっと )
(Motto)
好き な だけ 愛 させ て
Let me love you as much as I want!
ぐるぐる 脳内 きみ だらけ
Dizzy, my brain is full of you!
どうか し てる わ ね 私 ？
Am I going crazy?
心臓 ドキドキ 鳴っ てる 警報
My heart is beating like an alarm!
まいにち 幻覚 あらわれ て
Hallucinations appearing every day,
頭 に 花咲い いっ ちゃ って
Flowers blooming in my head—
恋 って やつ は 非常識 です わ ！
This thing called love is irrational!
いっそ 食べ ちゃう たい
I want to gobble you right up!
フリーズ し た 感情
My frozen emotions...
誰 も が 持っ てる お願い
Everyone's hidden wish.
じゅんじゅん 呪文 詠唱
Chanting a spell, heartbeat rising,
堂々 し て 急 上昇
Proudly shooting straight up!
これ が 恋 なら もう 後悔 し ない わ
If this is love, I won't regret it!
だ ・ か ・ ら
That's why—
君 の こと だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だ ・ い ・ す ・ き
I love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れる この ( 愛 は )
This overflowing (love)
きっと ( ずっと )
Will surely (last forever)
も～ 止まらない ( fooo ！ )
Never stopping! (Fooo!)
あいあい あいあい あいらぶゆー
Ai-ai, ai-ai, I love you!
君 が あいあい あいあい あい にじゅー
You say ai-ai, ai-ai, I need you!
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！ )
(Motto!)
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！ )
(Motto!)
好き な だけ 愛 さ せ て
Let me love you as much as I want!
揺れる ハート が ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My trembling heart goes pyon-pyon-pyon!
穴 に 落ち て あびゃびゃ
Falling into a pit, abya-bya!
こんな に なっ て も 未だ 抜け出せ ない
Even like this, I still can't escape!
( yeah ！ )
(Yeah!)
どうし た もん かね ぬいぬい ぬい
What on earth should I do, nui-nui-nui?
助け て きみ た ぴ ahoy hoy
Help me, youta-pi, ahoy hoy!
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！ )
(Motto!)
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！ )
(Motto!)
好き な だけ 愛し て ね
Love me as much as you want, okay?
ふわふわ 浮かぶ 夢 の 中
Floating softly in a dream,
きみ の 声 で 目 が 覚め た
I woke up to your voice.
五感 ぜんぶ が 君 な シグナル
All my senses are signals of you.
毎回 お騒がせ ごめん
Sorry for causing a fuss every time.
キュン で 壊れ ちゃい そう だ
It feels like my heart will break from cuteness!
恋 って やつ は 制御 不能 です わ ！
This thing called love is uncontrollable!
いっそ 抱きしめ て
Just hold me tight instead,
壊し て も いい よ
You can even break me.
誰 に も 邪魔 は させ ない
I won't let anyone get in our way.
ピチピチ 感情 で
With vibrant emotions,
ギラギラ 急 展開
A dazzling, sudden development.
これ が 運命 なら もう 迷わ ない
If this is destiny, I won't hesitate anymore.
── 覚悟 し て ね
──Be prepared, okay?
君 だけ が だいいちゅき だいいちゅき だいいちゅき だいいちゅき だいいちゅき だ ・ い ・ ちゅ ・ き
You're the only one I adore so much!
私 の この ( 愛 は )
My (love)
きっと ( ずっと )
Will surely (last forever)
も～ 離さない ( fooo ！！ )
Never let go! (Fooo!!)
be be be my baby
and kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss me
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！！ )
(Motto!!)
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！！ )
(Motto!!)
私 だけ を 見 て て ね
Only look at me, okay?
無視 太郎 は 泣い ちゃう かも ね
Mushitarou might cry, you know.
だって そんな の って ない ぺこ じゃん
Because that wouldn't be fair, peko!
わかっ てる よ ね ？ ダーリン ！
You understand, right? Darling!
いつ パイ 愛 を 待っ て ます ぅ ( ノエル ！)
Waiting for your love! (Noel!)
もっと ( ぺこら ！)
Motto (Pekora!)
もっと ( フレア ！)
Motto (Flare!)
もっと ( マリン ！)
Motto (Marine!)
もっと ホロライブ ファンタジー を ？ ( 愛し てるー ！)
More Hololive Fantasy? (We love you!)
君 の こと だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だ ・ い ・ す ・ き
I love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れる この ( 愛 は )
This overflowing (love)
きっと ( ずっと )
Will surely (last forever)
も～ 止まらない ( fooo ！ )
Never stopping! (Fooo!)
あいあい あいあい あいらぶゆー
Ai-ai, ai-ai, I love you!
君 が あいあい あいあい あい にじゅー
You say ai-ai, ai-ai, I need you!
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！)
(Motto!)
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！)
(Motto!)
好き な だけ 愛 さ せ て
Let me love you as much as I want!
ときめく ハート が ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My fluttering heart goes pyon-pyon-pyon!
矢 に 撃たれ て あびゃびゃ
Pierced by an arrow, abya-bya!
こんな に なっ たら 魔法 は 解け ましょ ～ ん
Once it comes to this, the magic won't wear off~!
( yeah ！)
(Yeah!)
本気 に なっ てる ぬいぬい ぬい ！
I'm getting serious, nui-nui-nui!
いつでも そば で ahoy hoy
Always by your side, ahoy hoy!
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！)
(Motto!)
もっと
Motto
( もっと ！)
(Motto!)
好き な だけ 愛し て ね
Love me as much as you want, okay?
私 達 の 愛 を もっと
Give us even more of your love!
みなさん次今度は白上フブキと
Everyone, next up is Shirakami Fubuki!
みなさん次今度は宝鐘マリンです！
And everyone, next up is Houshou Marine!
ついに私たちのデュエットだよ！最高に盛り上がって行こう！
Finally, our duet! Let's get hyped to the max!
ワン！ツー！３！ヘイ！イェーイ！
One, two, three! Hey! Yay!
ねえそこのお嬢さんここはもうスパラダイス
Hey there, young lady, this is already a super paradise!
不満げな顔しちゃダメだよダメダメ
Don't make an unhappy face, no, no, no!
スマイルがパスポートそれがなければつまんない
A smile is your passport, without it life is boring!
楽しんで行こうよバラ色ライフんなっちゃった
Let's enjoy a rosy life—it happened!
んなっちゃった
It happened!
勇気出してワンステップ イェーイ！
Take a courageous step, yay!
今までの景色とは明らかに違う世界
A world clearly different from the scenery until now.
フルブーストで楽しもうよ
Let's enjoy it with full boost!
ワン！ツー！スリー！でハイ！Happiness World
One, two, three! Hai! Happiness World!
いまだけはチャンスだ 夢をつかまえろ
This is our chance, catch your dream!
明日から 神吹雪
Starting tomorrow, a divine blizzard!
心配事したことない出来事が人待ってるさ
Events like you've never worried about await us.
信頼ソングで心躍らせ
Let your heart dance with a trust song,
ポジティブにさぁ思う存分気持ち晴れわたるその瞬間
Positively, let your feelings clear up to the fullest in that moment!
ぜんそくぜんしんだって１人じゃない
Even running at full breath, you're not alone.
私達と一緒に最初にハッピーな人生を！イェーイ！
Let's live a super happy life together with us! Yay!
ああ 寝足りない ずっとベッドにいたくない
Ah, I didn't sleep enough, I don't want to stay in bed!
眠くない？ 今日は休みなんだ ついついバイバイ
Not sleepy? Today's a day off, so bye-bye!
そんなときはそう 何かやりたいことやってみよう
At times like that, let's try doing something we want to do,
消化していこう 君の内に秘める欲望
And fulfill the desires hidden deep within you!
そういうときはそう 何かやりたいことやってみよう
At times like that, let's try doing something we want to do,
消化していこう 君の内に秘める欲望
And fulfill the desires hidden deep within you!
あまい ティー ティー 声を出して 水中は イエイ！
Sweet tea, tea! Raise your voice, underwater, yeah!
恥ずかしい気持ちとは 今すぐバイバイさ
Say bye-bye right now to any feelings of embarrassment!
エンジン全開 弾けようよ 1, 2, 3 で Happiness World!
Full throttle, let's burst with energy, 1, 2, 3 to Happiness World!
すすめ がむしゃらにいこう 立ち止まるな君
Push forward recklessly, don't stop for a moment!
未来への扉叩くだけ 簡単 一秒も無駄にはできないよ
Just knocking on the future's door—simple! Not a single second can be wasted.
顔を上げろ お宝へ出航 今回失敗したくない
Lift your face, set sail for the treasure! That desire not to fail this time
その想いは 追い風になる 新た思い出して 私たちがいるから
Will become a tailwind. Remember it anew, because we are here!
最高にハッピーな運命を イエイ！
To the happiest destiny, yeah!
みなさん次早口ですよ
Everyone, next is a tongue-twister!
マリンちゃん変わらないでね
Marine-chan, don't change!
船長は噛みませんよ
The captain never stumbles!
フブキちゃん噛みますよ
Fubuki-chan will stumble!
本当のこと大丈夫ですか？
Is everything really okay?
大丈夫 任せてください！
It's fine, leave it to us!
年がら年中 一緒にショータイム 来るもの拒まず いつもオールライ
Year-round, showtime together! We turn no one away, always alright!
バイブスは最高潮のね みんなで オーイエイ！
Vibes are at their peak, everyone, oh yeah!
手々を上げましょう ばんざい まだまだこれでももの足りない
Raise your hands, banzai! Still not enough with just this,
内気脱ぎ捨て そこどきに 恋しようぜ ここんとこ大路 老若男女
Shed your shyness, time to fall in love! On this grand road, men and women of all ages,
楽しいことがいちばん でしょ 少しだけ顔を外してみましょう
Having fun is the best, right? Let's take off our masks just a little bit,
夜ごと ワンダーランド
Wonderland every night!
今日もめいっぱい今踏み出せば きっと 人生の経験値GET中
If we step out with all our might today, for sure we'll gain experience in life!
少しした何気ないことだって 多分 笑えるさ
Even the little insignificant things will probably make us laugh.
いまだって 挑戦だ 夢をつかもう
Right now is the time, let's take on the challenge and seize our dreams!
明日から 神吹雪
Starting tomorrow, a divine blizzard!
想像したことない出来事が きっと待ってるさ
Unimagined events are surely waiting for us!
好きな歌で心おどらせ 飛びきりに楽しもう
Let your heart dance to your favorite song, let's enjoy it to the fullest!
気持ちは晴れわたる その瞬間
At that moment when your feelings clear up,
全身全霊 進んだ
We pushed forward with all our body and soul!
私たちと一緒に最高にハッピーな人生を イエイ！
Together with us, to the happiest life, yeah!
みんなでハッピーな人生を イエイ！
Everyone, to a happy life, yeah!
はい、ということで、改めまして皆さん！
Yes! So, once again, everyone—!
宝鐘マリンです！
I'm Houshou Marine!
白上フブキです！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
ふふふ、二人で！ ここ狐ね！
Hehe, the two of us! Here are the foxes!
後ろ髪吹雪でしょ！
It's "ukikami fubuki"!
サイリウム消して！ サイリウム消して！ 後ろの、後ろの、ほら、ほら、ほら！
Turn off your penlights! Turn off your penlights! In the back, look, look, look!
白上フブキこう！
Shirakami Fubuki like this!
いや違うでしょ、馬鹿野郎！ はい、じゃあ皆さんサイリウム消してください！
No that's wrong, you idiot! Okay, everyone please turn off your penlights!
ということで改めまして！ 後ろ髪吹雪と、宝鐘マリンです！
So once again, we are Ukikami Fubuki and Houshou Marine!
ポーズがちょっとついにしてみた
We tried doing a pose finally.
ちょっとバランス見て、ねむきみみたいな…
Let's check the balance, like "nemukimi"...
ということでね、やっとお届けしました！
So anyway, we finally delivered it!
いや、この曲ね、知ってますよね？ 知らないといないでしょうね！
Well, you all know this song, right? Nobody wouldn't know it!
もぐりだぞ、お前らって！
You'd be a poser if you didn't!
この曲ね、来週にね発表されて、我々もね、ずっとラジオやってますから
This song was announced next week, and since we've been doing radio for so long—
絆だよ絆！ そうです、そうですね！
It's about bonds! That's right, exactly!
あれ？これビジネスフレンドじゃない？
Huh? Aren't these business friends?
もちろん！ ちょっと曲がちょっとまずい！ やばい！ やめてください！
Of course! Wait, the song is a bit awkward! Oh no! Please stop!
ま、でもね、まりちゃん ついに、ついにですね！ 始まりました！
Well, but, Mari-chan, finally, it has begun!
１２３！ イエイ！
One, two, three! Yay!
ありがとうございます！おめでとうございます！
Thank you very much! Congratulations!
いや本当にね、いろいろ練習してきたけどさ、ダンスどうだった？
Seriously, we practiced all sorts of things, how was the dancing?
いや、ハッピーワールドさ…
Well, Happiness World...
ちょっとね、あの、怪しいところあったんだけど、
Wait, you know, there was a sketchy part,
マリーンちゃんの方全然見れてなくて、
but Marine-chan's wasn't shown at all!
センチョウも実はフブチャンのこと全然見れてなかったけど、
Senchou's actually wasn't shown at all, either.
センチョウは、
Senchou,
なんか最後の最後のラサビになって急に、
like, during the very last raspy rap part,
あれ、なんだっけってなって、
suddenly "Wait, what was it again?"
なんか、あれちょっと待て、あれあれあれあれあれ、あれこうだ、あれ次なんだっけみたいな、
Like, "Wait, how does it go? Wait, wait, wait, wait, what's next?"
アセリが出てちょっとわかんなくなっ、
A choreo came up and I was like "Oh."
でも可愛いことありますもねー。
Well, it's cute though, right?
まあ、なんかね、ちょっとそのちょっと遅れちゃったりね、できてないところまでかわいい！
Well, you know, being a little late or whatever, it's cute up to the parts you couldn't do!
優勝！優勝！
MVP! MVP!
それはかわいくにょーいって！
That's so cute!
待って！待って！ライブだぞ！やめるんだ！
Hey, this is a live! Stop it!
いやでもふぶちゃん、サードレスはね、
Well Fubuki-chan, as for the third song,
うん。
oops,
なんと言っても、やっぱり4期生や
even so, like the 4th generation, 5th generation,
5期生、それにENやIDのみんな、
and EN and ID everyone,
そう！がいにね、やっと次だよ！同じ！同じに同じに！わあー！やったー！
finally, FINALLY, next is... same! Same, same, same!
これは超楽しみですよねー！
This is super exciting, isn't it?
いやもう本当に、もうそうそうドキドキで、この後もね、我々ソロ曲もありますしね。
Yeah, yeah, we're really, like, super dokidoki, and after this, you know, we have solo songs too!
そうそう。
That's right.
Fubuki-chan is a bit like, "My turn is already over,"
It feels like Fubuki's turn is already over,
みたいな空気になっちゃってるけど、
like that kind of vibe.
まだソロ曲ありますからね！
There are more solo songs, you know!
始まったばっかですからね、本当に。
It just started, after all!
どんなユニットが来るかとかもね。
Who knows what kind of units are coming, too.
そうそうそう、ぜひね、
Yeah, yeah, yeah, please,
ちょっとぜひ予想して、ま、でも我々がもうここでね、終わっちゃった、終わっちゃったんでね、もうこんなこと言うのが、
well, but we already finished here, so we shouldn't be saying things like "it's over."
わかっちゃったけど。
Oops, we already figured it out!
え、でもこれっきりってこと？
Wait, does that mean you're done?
そういうこと？
Is that what that means?
マリンちゃん？
Marine-chan,
え、もしかしてビジネスレディオだったの白上と？
Wait, is it Business Radio with Shirakami?
そんなわけないじゃん！
No way, no way!
いや、ちょっとライブでテンション上がって、変な風になってるぞ。
Hey, my tension got too high on live stream and I'm acting all weird.
え、それ立て直してよ。
Wait, pull yourself together!
いや、もうね、でもこの後も本当にいろんなね、
Yeah, well, you know, but after this too, truly, various...
そう、メンバーが歌いますので！
members will sing,
まだまだここでね、気合入れちゃダメですからね、皆さん！
so we shouldn't get too pumped up yet, everyone!
こんな広い会場で、ちょっともう、
In such a huge venue,
なんでも、
what is it?
めちゃめちゃ広いよ、だって。
It's super huge,
ちょっとね、動き回る。
we're moving around a lot.
動き回る！待って待って、白上！
Wait, wait, Shirakami,
待って待って、来ないで！来ないで！
don't run around!
やめて！もう、足が相当、やばい、足。
My legs are worn out.
めちゃくちゃ使い果たしとるし。
We're totally exhausted!
すごく広いライブ会場で、ちょっとババ散らかさんでもろて。
It's so huge, at this live venue, running around like stray cats.
ちょっとあっちこっち、あっちこっち。
Let's go this way and that way!
アピール！アピール！
Appeal! Appeal!
君たち見えとるかー？見えとるかー？
Can you guys see us? Can you see us?
ちょっと、あの、大丈夫ですか？あの、おばあちゃんですか？
Wait, are you okay? Are you an old lady?
確かに、ちょっとね、ちょっとね、ちょっとあっちこっち散らかさないでいただいて。
That's funny. Just don't run around everywhere, please.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
この後ソロ曲もある、ぴったりでしょ？
There are solo songs, too, right?
あ、そうそう、ソロ曲もあるからね、みんなね、ちょっとね。
Oh right, there are solo songs too, so everyone, you know...
ねえ。そう、いったい何を歌うんでしょうかね、ソロ曲ね。
So, what are we going to sing for the solo songs?
えーでもやっぱセンチョウ、ふぶちゃんは、
Well, but Senchou, Fuubuu-chan,
ちょっとぶっちゃけあれかなって思ってるの。
I'm wondering if it's that one.
あれってなんだろう？
"Are?" What is that?
あれって何かな？
"Are," what could it be?
マリンちゃんはあれかな？
Marine-chan, is it "Are"?
いや、ちょっと待って、そのあれじゃないかも。
Yeah, wait a second, maybe it's not "Are."
あ、でも、なんか、リハーサルの時とかなんか、あれ？
Ah, but it was like during rehearsals and stuff, like...
いや、ちょっとね、君たちはあれだと思ってるんだろうな。
Well, you guys probably think it's "Are,"
あれだろと、あれだろと思ってるんだろうな。
Thinking it's "Are" and "Are."
ちょっと気まずすぎる。でもあれじゃないんだ、気まずいな。
It's a bit awkward, but it's actually not "Are." It's kind of awkward.
後ろ髪はね、みんなの予想してるあれだと思うので、ぜひねいっぱいサイリウム振ってくださいね。
As for us, we're expecting it to be "Are," so everyone, please swing your Cyalumes a lot!
なんか、まるで
It's kind of like...
センチョウもあれです、センチョウもあれで。
Senchou's is also "Are."
あれってなんだ？負けられない。
"Are"? I can't lose!
他のメンバーの曲もね、まだだって今、2曲目ですよ、まだ。
Well, other members' songs are still... this is only the second song!
まだまだ2曲目ですからね！
Still only the second song, you know!
ていうかさ、よく考えたらさ、
And, thinking about it,
SSSをさ、早速消化しちゃったけど、どうすんのこの先？
SSS, we already introduced it, so what are we going to do from now on?
確かに、この後も全体曲？
True, what about after this, the rest of the songs?
そうよ。
That's right.
あ、どうしよう。わからない、なんか。
Ah, what should I do? I don't know, what...
あ、わかった。あ、ということ、そろそろお時間。
Oh, I see. Well then, it's about time.
次の曲、次の曲、次の曲、行ってみましょう！
Next song, next song, let's go!
行きますか！
Let's go!
皆さんね、どんどん盛り上がっていってくださいね！
Everyone, get more and more pumped up, okay?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
せーの！
Ready, go!
つながるホロライブ！
Tsunagaru Hollolive!
バスっ、あ、散らかし！散らかし！散らかし！
Busst... Oh, stray cat, stray cat!
散らかし！
Stray cat!
咲き乱れる花火、下駄を鳴らし
Blooming fireworks, clattering geta sandals,
澄んだ夜空見上げ袖振った
looking up at the clear night sky, I waved my sleeves.
今日はきっと、そう言えるかな?
Is today for sure, can I say that?
迷える音色は恋の囮
The wavering melody is the decoy of love.
結んだ髪、浴衣着付けて
Tied-up hair, putting on a yukata,
鏡の前では晴れ姿
a bright look in front of the mirror.
あっぱれ!あっぱれ!あなたに
Apare! Apare! For you!
一日千秋、一心不乱に無我夢中に
A thousand days in a single moment, single-mindedly, wholeheartedly,
待ちに待っていた夏祭り
the summer festival I've been waiting for.
歩く度、鼻緒を気にして
With every step, minding my nose,
やっぱり?やっぱり?私は
is it really? really? for me?
七転八倒、艱難辛苦で四苦八苦
Falling down seven times and getting up eight, through hardships and trials,
夕暮れに頬が染まってく
cheeks dyed in the twilight.
色付いた二人の心揺るる
Stirring the hearts of two colored people,
特別な夜に言葉を紡ぐ
spinning words into a special night.
咲き乱れる花火、下駄を鳴らし
Blooming fireworks, clattering geta sandals,
澄んだ夜空見上げ袖振った
looking up at the clear night sky, I waved my sleeves.
今日はきっと、そう言えるかな?
Is today for sure, can I say that?
迷える音色は恋の囮
The wavering melody is the decoy of love.
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」ってぽいな
Love's spoiler, looks like "we're breaking up"
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」ってぽいな
Life's spoiler, looks like "we're dying"
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん…
What's that, so deep and cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ
Dancing to a collection of buzzwords
失敬
Pardon me
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-tu-ru-tu-tu-ru style...
ざっとでも壁際死地で乱雑
Even roughly, chaotic at death's door
鮮血バジ読書 生存乱雑ダディ
Fresh blood, voracious reading, messy survival
楽しもう
Let's enjoy it
おもしろがれること探し構えおば
Search for amusement, get ready
返事聞かせてくれ
Let me hear your reply
決めつけて一瞬
Deciding in an instant
摘み食い辛口反射 ライダー ワクワクしてんだ
Snacking on spicy reflex, getting excited
みんな かき混ぜていくぞ
Everyone, stirring it up!
せーの 神っ!
Ready, God-ish!
結構手遅れだ
Quite overdue
天井ですなんだよそれ
Hitting pity? What's that supposed to mean?
いっちょためたおばか
You fool who saved it up
パワースゴイありがと
So much power, thank you
響きこえて全方位ご挨拶
Resounding in all directions, greetings
こうしちゃいられないなもんで
We can't just stay like this, so
息がどんどん出だすもんで
Breath keeps rushing out
四方にぷりりアンテナ張っているくじゃん
Antennae stretched out in all directions, right?
いつでも心はちゃんと純粋で
Always, my heart is purely and truly
いったいなの？好奇心は絶えずねじんで
What is this? Curiosity twists endlessly
痛いなって息継ぎ越せるん堂
"It hurts," getting through breaths
調子に乗ったらすぐあきらめちゃうから
If I get carried away, I'll give up right away
ああ 最低な戻ってこい人生
Ah, worst possible life, come back
せーの バジ読者 生存乱雑ダディ
Ready, voracious reader, messy survival
しっかりつけ努力とは最後まであきらめないこと
Hold on tight, effort means never giving up
メモっておいて本当はビビって自信なんかないよ本当はビビって不安ばっかで泣きそうだってもねベイビー
Make a note of it: honestly I'm scared, full of anxiety, like I'm gonna cry, but hey baby
くじけないって決めたの だからベイビー 調子したいよ見習いの手 無限のビートで
I decided not to break, so baby, with infinite beat
全身ちゃんときゃんけして
Connect your whole body properly
高くまでかいけそうぞ
It feels like we can reach high
ちゃんと京都して
Face each other properly
特殊しよう
Let's customize
僕が弱んだも本当にするんだもん
Even if I sounded weak, I'll make it real
現実越えの未来
A future beyond reality
ざっとでも壁際死地で乱雑
Even roughly, chaotic at death's door
鮮血バジ読者 生存乱雑ダディ
Fresh blood, voracious reading, messy survival
楽しもう
Let's enjoy it
おもしろがれること探し答え出してせーの
Search for amusement, find the answer, ready, go!
無限のフィールドで
In an infinite field
タイミング失ってもいい
It's okay to lose your timing
止まらすかい一瞬
Don't stop for a single instant
つまりこれが僕の答えなんだ胸を張れ今を生きるその意味を
In short, this is my answer. Stick out your chest, and live in the present
明る日も暗い日も確かめて進め
Verify the bright days and dark days, and move forward
笑え！
Laugh!
ウェルカム！ あなたが選ばしポルカサガス
Welcome! You chose Polka's quest
今盛りのお客さま！
Customers in their prime right now!
やっとお待たせしました！
We finally kept you waiting!
とってもハッピーなアイドル 愉快で可愛いアイドル
A very happy idol, cheerful and cute idol
そして今はポルカサガス！
And right now, Polka quest!
何が見たい？ どんなことでも仕上げる
What do you want to see? I'll make anything happen
私は座長 その名もオマールポルカ
I am the ringmaster, by the name of Omaru Polka
絶対笑顔にさせちゃうスマイル！
I'll definitely make you smile!
それじゃ最後までライブ楽しんでこうぜ
Well then, let's enjoy the live all the way to the end
準備はできてるか？ Are you ready?
Are you ready?
さあ近くにおいで 聴いて
Come closer and listen
一人誰もが狂点 疾走電界 禍の始まりさ
Everyone goes crazy, speeding electric field, the beginning of disaster
ぐっと惹かれるでしょ？ 音を抑えてね
You're drawn right in, right? Keep the volume down
それでは準備をしてさ
Well then, get ready and
いっぱい動物たち たまにピエロ
Lots of animals, occasionally a clown
ハラハラドキドキしちゃうでしょ
It's thrilling and heart-pounding, isn't it?
禍な枠踏ませ 綱渡りして
Stepping out of bounds, tightrope walking
ちょっとぐらいの同士なんて怖いいいよ
Even a little companionship is scary, but it's okay
カモンライオン！
Come on, Lion!
とっておきのライブ もっと最高で もっと最高を 手を叩こう
A special live performance, even greater, even greater, let's clap our hands
ほら本気で置いて
Look, really leave it behind
えんもたけなわなサーカスへどうぞ
Welcome to the height of the circus!
だけだよホログラムみたい
It's just like a hologram!
なきがら奇跡が踊る
Miracles dance upon remains.
いつかは世界をとりこにしちゃうぞ
Someday, we'll captivate the entire world!
あしたの演目はどうしようかな
What should tomorrow's program be?
屋根裏で秘密の作戦会議さ
A secret strategy meeting in the attic.
いっぱいの観客席が驚くような
Enough to astonish a full audience,
飛び切りのショーを見せましょ
Let's put on an extraordinary show!
思い出したらじっとしてられない
Once I remember, I can't stay still.
さあ、引率して Let's Go!
Now, lead the way and let's go!
これがやりたい、これがやりたい
This is what I want to do, over and over,
そして時間て足りないの
And yet, there's never enough time.
みんなの好きな色は何?
What is everyone's favorite color?
ボルカはもちろんレッド、赤!
For Polka, of course, it's red!
はい!一緒に届けよう、ありがとう
Yes! Let's deliver it together, thank you!
みんなの好きな色をたくさん教えて
Tell me lots of everyone's favorite colors!
その手を強く伸ばして
Stretch out your hands firmly,
上手くいかなくて
Even when things don't go well,
空回ってばかりで
And I just spin my wheels in circles,
少し落ち込んじゃう日もあるけれど
There are days when I feel a bit down,
見ててね、大丈夫、いつまでも
But watch me, it's okay, always.
強くよしでラッキーシ
Strongly determined, lucky day!
顔を上げて、今日のステージがほら
Lift your head, look—today's stage
ねぇ待てるのさ
Is waiting for you!
ポルカ?オルカ?ポルカオルカ!
Polka? Orca? Polka, Orca!
ポルカ、オルカ、ポルカ、歌うぞ!
Polka, Orca, Polka, let's sing!
はい!はい!はい!はい!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
みんな手拍子してください!
Everyone, please clap your hands!
ポルカオルカ?ポルカオルカ!
Polka, Orca? Polka, Orca!
ポルカオルカ、ポルカ踊ろう!
Polka, Orca, let's dance Polka!
うん、ポルカ、ポルカオルカ!
Yeah, Polka, Polka, Orca!
ポルカオルカ、ポルカ踊ろう!
Polka, Orca, let's dance Polka!
強く強く願うんだ
Wishing strongly, so strongly,
どんな夢だってきっときっと叶うはず
Any dream is sure to come true.
何も怖くない、みんなの声は全部ちゃんと届いてるよ!
There's nothing to fear, everyone's voices all reach me!
さあ、新しい次元、新しい舞台へもっともっと突き進もう!
Now, let's press further ahead into a new stage!
まだまだ付いておいで、笑い転げちゃうサーカスへ
Keep following along to this uproarious circus,
ここだけだよ、はじめての仲間、景色に
Only here, with first-time friends and scenery,
こころも踊る、今にも世界中をとりこにしちゃうから
Our hearts dance as we're about to captivate the world!
目を離さないでね、大丈夫、いつまでも
Don't take your eyes off me, it's okay, always,
強くよしでラッキーシ、顔を上げて、今日のステージがほら待てるのさ!
Strongly determined, lucky day—today's stage is waiting!
強く強く願うんだ
Wishing strongly, so strongly,
どんな夢だってきっときっと叶うはず
Any dream is sure to come true.
何も怖くない、みんなの声は全部ちゃんと届いてるよ!
There's nothing to fear, everyone's voices all reach me!
さあ、新しい次元、新しい舞台へもっともっと突き進もう!
Now, let's press further ahead into a new stage!
まだまだ付いておいで、笑い転げちゃうサーカスへ
Keep following along to this uproarious circus,
ここだけだよ、はじめての仲間、景色に
Only here, with first-time friends and scenery,
こころも踊る、今にも世界中をとりこにしちゃうから
Our hearts dance as we're about to captivate the world!
目を離さないでね、大丈夫、いつまでも
Don't take your eyes off me, it's okay, always,
強くよしでラッキーシ、顔を上げて、今日のステージがほら待てるのさ!
Strongly determined, lucky day—today's stage is waiting!
ポルカ?オルカ?ポルカオルカ!
Polka? Orca? Polka, Orca!
ポルカ、オルカ、ポルカ、歌うぞ!
Polka, Orca, Polka, let's sing!
はい!はい!はい!はい!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
みんな手拍子してください!
Everyone, please clap your hands!
ポルカオルカ?ポルカオルカ!
Polka, Orca? Polka, Orca!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wag your tail and scout!
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encounter more cute girls!
集まれちゃえば最強だよ！
Once they gather, it's the strongest!
文化祭が始まる
The school festival is beginning.
最高規模でいきたいの
I want to go on the grandest scale.
君も参加してね
You should participate too!
ネットチケット無制限
Unlimited net tickets!
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal is surprised.
キャスト足りない大焦り
Panicking over a lack of cast members.
ワンワン泣いちゃうううう
Crying woof-woof!
本番間近はキキキ
As the show nears, it's crunch time.
運営の予算はギリギリ
The management's budget is razor-thin.
すねちゃうぞ 泣いちゃうぞ
I'll pout, I'll cry!
テレフォンナンバー ピピピピピ
Telephone number, pi-pi-pi-pi-pi.
「イケてる子を用意して」
"Prepare some cool kids!"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer.
可愛い子チェック！スカウト！
Cute girl check! Scout!
超超超超超超超美少女ゲットだぜー☆
Got a super-duper mega bishoujo-☆
(美少女捕まえた☆)
(Caught a bishoujo-☆)
もしもし私が死んだ ならば
If I were to ever die,
バーチャル葬で派手にねっ♡
Throw me a flashy virtual funeral♡
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how serious I want to be about this.
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wag your tail and scout!
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encounter more cute girls!
集まれちゃえば最強だよ！
Once they gather, it's the strongest!
あー無駄足三昧面倒いな
Ah, running around in vain is such a pain,
どうしようもない焦燥感
With this helpless feeling of impatience.
タイムリミットは後ちょっと！？
Is the time limit just a bit away!?
ここらで早もういっちょ！？
Let's go for one more right here!?
気が付いたらライフも 少ししかない
Before I knew it, I had barely any life left
そしていつもそこでいい感づかう
And I'm always paying attention right there
諦めずにエアマウンテンまで辿り着くけれど
I make it to Air Mountain without giving up, but
すぐにざんぎなくなる
I quickly run out of HP
良いシールドがあれば楽にエアマウンテンは倒せるけど
If I had a good shield, I could easily beat Air Mountain, but
何回やっても 何回やっても うとまる
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try...
倒せないよ 落ちるころは
I can't defeat it, when I fall off
何回やってもよければい 後ろに下がって
No matter how many times, if it's okay, I step back
距離をとっても いずれは距離を詰められる
Even if I keep my distance, the distance will eventually close in
タイムレオンを試してみたけど あいつのジャンプをくれない
I tried Time Leon, but I couldn't dodge his jump
だから次次は絶対カスタムに
So next time I'll definitely customize it
僕はいいかんだけは最後まで取っておくぞ
I'll save my good intuition until the very end!
アイテム二号があれば楽に向こうの岸まで届くけど
If I had Item No. 2, I could easily reach the opposite shore, but
何回やっても 何回やっても えあうまうんが倒せないよ
No matter how many times I try, I can't defeat Air Mountain
あの竜巻何回やってもよければい 後ろに
That tornado, no matter how many times I try, stepping back...
回って打ち続けても いずれは風に飛ばされる
Even if I keep spinning and shooting, I'll eventually be blown away
タイムレオンでも試してみたけど 竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
I tried Time Leon too, but it's useless against a tornado
だから次次は絶対カスタムに
So next time I'll definitely customize it
僕はいいかんだけは最後まで取っておくぞ
I'll save my good intuition until the very end!
倒せないよ
I can't defeat it!
みんな！いっぱいいっぱい 指ありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you so much for the fingers!
こんなに指がもらえるなんてこりゃ幸せです
To receive this many fingers makes me so happy!
みんなが痛みに耐えて切り落としてくれた指 大事にするからね！
I'll cherish the fingers you endured the pain to cut off for me!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ぐるぐる回る 時計の針の音 地球の風の音
Spinning around, the tick of clock hands, the sound of Earth's wind
変わる景色を楽しみながらこんなところまで来た
Enjoying the changing scenery, I've come this far
時の流れはいつでもゆっくり だけどハートの動くスピード気まぐれは
The flow of time is always slow, but the beating speed of my heart is whimsical
聞かせてよ この場所へちゃんと届くように
Let me hear it, so it reaches this place properly
君のクララララメリゴララキャリゴララ
Your merry-go-round, carry-go-round
夢のようなスピードでエスコートして 飛び立った後の歌に乗り込めばいけるんだ
Escort me at a dreamlike speed, if we board the song after taking off, we can make it!
はい結び求められない
Yes, ties are not demanded
さあ来いメリゴララ キャリゴララ パレードは始まりのベルが鳴り響く夜に
Come on, merry-go-round, carry-go-round, the parade begins on a night when the bell rings
迎えに行こうよ 同じスピードでひとつのナンバー奏でよう
Let's go meet them, playing a single number at the same speed
ハートを1ミリでも動かせば 奇跡を起こす大きな一歩につながるから
Even if we move our hearts just a millimeter, it connects to a big step that creates miracles
つまらないときも ワクワクを繰り出して
Even when it's boring, let out the excitement
moonlight merry-go-round
candy-go-round
ready-go-“live”
Ready go "live"
夢のようなスピードで エスコート
Escorting you at a dreamlike speed
時の流れは いつでもゆっくり
The flow of time is always slow
だけどハートの動く スピード 気まぐれ ワープ
But the heart's pace is a fickle warp
聞かせてよ この場所へ ちゃんと 届くように
Let me hear it so it reaches this place clearly
キミの clap-clap-clap
With your clap-clap-clap
everybody clap hands up
空想へドライブ★
Driving into fantasy★
moonlight merry-go-round
candy-go-round
ready-go-“live”
Ready go "live"
夢のようなスピードで 飛び立とう
Let's fly away at a dreamlike speed
歌に乗り込めば 行けるんだ
If we ride on the song, we can go anywhere
タイムスリップ もう止められない
Time slip, we can no longer stop it
starlight merry-go-round candy-go-round parallel-world
はじまりのベルが鳴り響く 夜に
The bell of beginnings rings out into the night
迎えに行くから
To welcome you
同じ ビートで ひとつの ナンバー 奏でよう
Let's play a single number to the same beat
ハートを1ミリでも 動かせば
If you move your heart even a millimeter
キセキ起こす 大きな1歩に 繋がるから
It connects to a big step that works miracles
つまらないときは 「わくわく」を クリックしてみよう
When you're bored, try clicking on "excitement"
キミと dance×dance×dance
With you, dance×dance×dance
ステップ 踏んで パーティーしよう！
Take a step and let's have a party!
stand up ring-a-bell fairy-tail wonderland-“live”
Stand up ring-a-bell fairy-tail wonderland-"live"
出掛けたい場所へ 連れてくよ
I'll take you to the place you want to go
瞳 閉じたら 合図 なんだ
When you close your eyes, that's the signal
妄想 トリップ もう 止められない
Delusion trip, we can no longer stop it
start line ring-a-bell fairy-tail colorful-night
どんな距離だって 越えて 会いに行く
No matter the distance, I'll cross it to meet you
夜空を見上げて
Looking up at the night sky
ドラマチックで 忘れられない 今にしよう
Let's make this present moment dramatic and unforgettable
起きても覚めない 魔法かけるから
I'll cast a magic spell that won't fade even when you wake up
はじめよう ステージを
Let's begin the stage
キミの胸のドキドキ
The pounding of your heart
嘘じゃないよ リアルだよ
It's no lie, it's real
星もうれしくて 飛び回ってるよ
Even the stars are happily flying around
リズムを合わせるように 飛びきりな 夢を
So that we match our rhythm, a supreme dream
キミとキミとキミと キミとキミと一緒に
Together with you, you, you, you, and you
moonlight merry-go-round
candy-go-round
ready-go-“live”
Ready go "live"
夢のようなスピードで 飛び立とう
Let's fly away at a dreamlike speed
歌に乗り込めば 行けるんだ
If we ride on the song, we can go anywhere
タイムスリップ もう止められない
Time slip, we can no longer stop it
starlight merry-go-round candy-go-round parallel-world
はじまりのベルが鳴り響く 夜に
The bell of beginnings rings out into the night
迎えに行くから
To welcome you
同じ ビートで ひとつの ナンバー
Playing a single number
奏でよう
To the same beat
はい！ということで、キャンディー・ゴー・ラウンドでしたー！
Alright, that was "Candy-Go-Round"!
いえーい！ありがとうございましたー！見たー！？
Yay! Thank you so much! Did you see that!?
すっごいデっけえ！
That was SO huge!
すごいよねー！
It's amazing!
ちょっとね、すごい大きい会場なんですけど！
It's a really, really big venue, you know!
じゃあ、改めてちょっと自己紹介していきましょっか！
Now then, let's do our self-introductions properly!
じゃあ、祭りからいきますよ。みんなペンライトをお祭り色に染めてくれー！
Alright, starting with Matsuri. Everyone, dye your penlights festival colors!
せーの、いきます！みんな、こんばんわっしょーい！
Ready, go! Everyone, evening Wasshoi!
どうも！ホロライブの清楚担当、みんなのアイドル夏色まつりでしたー！
Hello! Hololive's pure representative, everyone's idol Natsuiro Matsuri!
ということでね、祭り先輩、どうですかこの景色？
So, Matsuri-senpai, what do you think of this view?
いやもうすごい！もう何？もうわからん、この、この
Man, it's amazing! Like, what? I don't even know, this, this...
規模がわかんないよ！わかる！
The scale is incomprehensible! I know!
じゃあ、それをね、ねねちにも体感してもらいましょう！自己紹介どうぞ！
Well then, let's have Nenechi experience that too! Self-introduction, please!
やったー！みんなねねの色にしてねー！みんなこんねねー！
Yay! Everyone, make it Nene's color! Hello Nene everyone!
ホロライブのきせれ、オレンジ担当、アイドルVTuberの桃鈴ねねでーす！
Hololive's orange representative, idol VTuber Momosuzu Nene!
すごすぎ！
So amazing!
ねえ、感想すごすぎ！
Hey, that impression is too amazing!
語彙力なくなりますよ。確かに。広いからねー。
You lose your vocabulary. True. Because it's so wide.
それでは最後は！大空スバルー！ペンライトを黄色に変えてください！
And now for the last one! Oozora Subaru! Please change your penlights to yellow!
いくよ！ちはーっ！ホロライブ2期生大空スバル！オードレスバールー！
Here we go! Chi-hass! Hololive 2nd Gen Oozora Subaru! O-dre-Suba-ru!
やばっ！ねえ、やばいよね！よくわからん！
Whoa! Hey, this is crazy! I don't really get it!
いや、本当に実感がわかないまだ。
Man, it still doesn't feel real yet.
ちょっとせっかくだからさ、あのさ、ペンライトとさ、あのブロック分けした振り付けやろうよ！
Since we're here, why don't we do the choreography split by penlight blocks!
じゃあ座る、こっち担当。じゃあ真ん中ね。
Okay, Subaru, you take this side. And the middle.
いくよ！じゃあまずは、座る、側の人振ってー！
Here we go! First, everyone on Subaru's side, wave your lights!
ありがとー！じゃあ続いては、祭り先輩！
Thank you! Next up, Matsuri-senpai!
はい、じゃあ真ん中の人たちいくよ！うん。振れー！
Alright, now people in the middle, here we go! Yeah. Wave them!
めっちゃきれいだなー！
They're so pretty!
はい！じゃあ最後はねねちの側のひとー！
Alright! And finally, people on Nenechi's side!
moonlight merry-go-round candy-go-round ready-go- “ live ”
夢のようなスピードで エスコート
Escorting you at a dreamlike speed
さすがだ！みんな熱い！
Amazing! Everyone's so passionate!
泣いてた！
You were crying!
それじゃあ最後は全体で振りましょう！いくよー！せーの！
Now, let's all wave together for the final part! Here we go! Ready, set!
うわー！ / うおー！すげぇ！
Whoa! / Wow, incredible!
これやってみたかったんだよ、すばる！
I've always wanted to try this, Subaru!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
じゃあちょっとね、真ん中戻りましょ、戻りましょ戻りましょ。はい。
Alright, let's head back to the center. Let's go back.
ということでね、「Candy-Go-Round」披露させていただいたんですけど、どうだった？ちょっと踊ってみて、まつり先輩！
So, we performed "Candy-Go-Round", how was it? How was it dancing to it, Matsuri-senpai?
いやーね、めちゃめちゃ楽しかったね、あの、楽しかったよね。最初さ。
Man, it was super fun, yeah, it was fun. At first, you know...
最初レッスンのね、時ね、うん、もうここから入ったんですけど、「これやばくない！？」って思ったんだけど、うん、まあ
At the very first lesson, you know, when we started from here, I thought, "Isn't this crazy?!" But well...
あの、あれだね、意外にやってみると、ま、できちゃうのかな。
But you know, surprisingly, once you try it, well, you can manage it.
いや上手だったよ、ほんとに！えー、ほんと？ありがとう！
You were really good! - Eh, really? Thank you!
うれしいな。ガチでテレテレや。
I'm so happy. I'm genuinely blushing.
はい、じゃあ続いてね、どうでした？踊ってみて。
Alright, so next up, how was it dancing to it?
ねねはね、あのほら途中で真ん中に行くじゃんか。はいはいはい。あのときのね、あの、両端からのプレッシャー？
As for Nene, you know how we go to the center halfway through? Yeah, yeah. The pressure from both sides at that time?
あれやった、やった！やってみようよ。もういいよ！あーすごい熱！
We did that, yeah! Let's try it. That's enough! Ah, such heat!
先輩に挟まれし、こうやってね、みんなでこう、ぶつからないか心配でさ。真ん中やっぱ目立っちゃうから。
Sandwiched between my seniors, doing this together, I was worried about bumping into each other. The center stands out the most, after all.
確かにね！ミスできないプレッシャー。うん。でも、
That's true! The pressure of not making mistakes. Yeah. But...
すごくよかったと思います！そうの、ごまかした、ごまかした！ごまかしたこと言ったじゃん。
I think it went really well! - That's covering it up, you covered it up! You just said you covered it up.
ねねちゃんも聞いてみな！そう、聞いてみなよ。ねねちゃんはね、すごいあの会場に聞いてみる？
Ask Nene-chan too! Yeah, go ahead and ask. Nene-chan, should we ask the venue?
え、みんなどうだった？うんうん、うんうん。
Eh, how was everyone? Yeah, yeah.
会場に聞いてみよう。そう、聞いてみよう。そこが喋れなくちゃいけないじゃん、結局！
Let's ask the venue. Yeah, let's ask. Wait, you gotta speak too, after all!
まさにね、やっぱダンス上手な3人って言って運営さんにね、集められたからね、そりゃ完璧だよね！
Exactly, since the management gathered the three best dancers, of course it's perfection!
そうよ。ちょっとあんまりあのいびらないで、もろせ。いびらないで、もろせってみんな。
That's right. Don't bully me too much, Morose. Everyone's saying don't bully Morose.
みんな、泣かないで！できてたよ、結構！すごい上手だった！めちゃめちゃ可愛かったし！
Everyone, don't cry! You did it, quite well! You were super good! And super cute!
ということでですね、すばるの前にもね、あのね、かなたん と、あとポルカちゃんと、あとね、こーねがね、それぞれね、
And so, before Subaru's group, you know, Kanatan, Polka-chan, and Corne, each of them...
個性的な世界観で、もうめちゃめちゃキャラクター濃かったから！
With their unique worldviews, their characters were so strong!
でもここからはね、すばるたちも頑張っていきましょうと意気込まれましたよ！いやそうだよね！
But from here on, we're gonna do our best too, as we were pumped up! - Yeah, exactly!
ということでですね、なんとですね、YouTubeのちら見せがここまでなんですよー！あーやだやだ！
And so, amazingly, the YouTube free preview ends right here! - Aw, no way!
いや、でもこれからも見たいよね！むしろね、こう見たい気持ちが高まってると思うのよ、みんな。
Well, but you want to keep watching, right? Actually, I think everyone's desire to watch more is growing.
みんな、わかってるよ。
Everyone knows it.
はい！そんな人はね、概要欄をチェックして、ここからのチケットを買ってください！
Yes! Such people, please check the description box and buy your tickets from here!
はい！ということでですね、そろそろお時間なので、まつり先輩締めてもらっていいですか？
Alright! And so, since it's about time, Matsuri-senpai, could you wrap things up for us?
はい、時間きちゃったということで、次の曲に行きましょうか！
Yes, since the time has come, let's move on to the next song!
それではいきましょう！せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set!
つながる ホロライブ
Connecting Hololive
ホロライブ！
Hololive!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
DAY 1 free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
DAY1 無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of DAY1 has ended. Thank you for watching!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
DAY1 free stream has ended. Thank you for watching!
DAY1無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part of DAY1 has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!